<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Gatsby Starter Business]]></title><description><![CDATA[Leverage Gatsby Business Starter for your Business.]]></description><link>https://gatsby-starter-business.netlify.com</link><image><url>https://gatsby-starter-business.netlify.com/icons/icon-512x512.png</url><title>Gatsby Starter Business</title><link>https://gatsby-starter-business.netlify.com</link></image><generator>GatsbyJS Business Starter</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2018 22:05:56 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gatsby-starter-business.netlify.com/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><author><![CDATA[Vaibhav Sharma]]></author><copyright><![CDATA[All rights reserved to RZAY TECHNOLOGIES, created with <3 at TALK, LLC]]></copyright><item><title><![CDATA[Brand Success: Only with the right consumer data]]></title><description><![CDATA[But how do you measure consumer retention and sales? Many brands still stick to outdated methods of gathering data that are unreliable and unsuccessful, reward programs provide little benefit in tracking consumer happiness, printed coupons frequently get lost and are difficult for consumers to keep track of and are even harder for businesses to keep track of, it becomes even worse when global…]]></description><link>https://gatsby-starter-business.netlify.com/blog/lorem-ipsum-dolor-situm.1/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://gatsby-starter-business.netlify.com/blog/lorem-ipsum-dolor-situm.1/</guid><category><![CDATA[consumer]]></category><category><![CDATA[data]]></category><category><![CDATA[brand success]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Vaibhav Sharma]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 22:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;But how do you measure consumer retention and sales? Many brands still stick to outdated methods of gathering data that are unreliable and unsuccessful, reward programs provide little benefit in tracking consumer happiness, printed coupons frequently get lost and are difficult for consumers to keep track of and are even harder for businesses to keep track of, it becomes even worse when global companies must keep track of all their regional promotions, some businesses have overcome these issues with their own satisfactory, albeit expensive and ineffective solutions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What is most surprising is brands and businesses continue to fail to utilize the one thing each customer possesses and uses daily, their phones. Whether receiving coupons, promotions, or entries into sweepstakes, case studies have shown that customer-business engagement increases dramatically. Consumers are actually 77% more likely to redeem a digital coupon over a paper coupon, providing drastic differences in results for those merchants, this has a significant impact on increasing sales and potentially improving brand’s margins.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Why stop there? SMS and social media are all powerful tools that leading companies are using to connect with their consumers, but many fail to use their true benefits beyond consumer engagement. When potential consumers are sent free top-ups, digital content, and the chance to win grand prizes for buying your brands, satisfaction increases among end-consumers. This engagement carries valuable data that can be used to analyze behavior and predict purchasing patterns and future decisions. With this data, our customers can realize tremendous gains. In just a few case studies, our customers who sell consumer goods such as international coffee, cosmetic, and biscuit brands have seen the overall traffic of 20 million transactions in four months just in Egypt. Another brand saw new user growth estimated at 450,000 on their Facebook promotion application installed on their fan page. These results are through SMS and Facebook alone as digital channels. The possibility of future growth based on additional technologies and analyses is an additional value that can be obtained through:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Effective tracking of product use and purchase&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Extensive analysis of key performance indicators&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Enhanced competitive positioning&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More efficient and affordable services when compared to expensive internal information systems and resources&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Consumers want more than just the products they buy; they want engagement. Our customers see significant boosts in consumer engagement, thus they’re always at the forefront of the competition. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more details visit iMakaseb.com&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[An International Coffee Brand to Engage Digitally with 5 million consumers in 4 months]]></title><description><![CDATA[A successful promotion is one which has mutual economic benefits for both parties. You are looking to increase your bottom line by getting your existing customers to repurchase. Your customer base is looking for their loyalty to be rewarded, which can often take the form of financial incentives to repurchase when you get it right, it is a win-win scenario. By understanding and then fulfilling your…]]></description><link>https://gatsby-starter-business.netlify.com/blog/lorem-ipsum-dolor-situm.2/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://gatsby-starter-business.netlify.com/blog/lorem-ipsum-dolor-situm.2/</guid><category><![CDATA[coffee]]></category><category><![CDATA[promotion]]></category><category><![CDATA[4 millions]]></category><dc:creator><![CDATA[Vaibhav Sharma]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 22:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;A successful promotion is one which has mutual economic benefits for both parties. You are looking to increase your bottom line by getting your existing customers to repurchase. Your customer base is looking for their loyalty to be rewarded, which can often take the form of financial incentives to repurchase when you get it right, it is a win-win scenario. By understanding and then fulfilling your customers&apos; needs on a regular basis, you will engender long-term customer loyalty.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Prior to using the services of iMakaseb, the coffee brand used the traditional way of distributing prizes employed for rewards using physical gifts, it was a nightmare, it was also characterized by a lot of shortcomings, cases of lost prizes and theft were a commonplace, it was impossible to keep a record of consumers using their products, there were no criteria or indicators for measuring the success of any previous promotion conducted, there was a lack of innovative tools needed to enhance their competitive position to help in future plans and forecasts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Through the collaboration of iMakaseb, the coffee brand&apos;s marketing executives were able to leverage online analytics and dashboard which resulted in building a consumer database and insights for future CRM activities, increased sales and increased efficiency in marketing spending, to the fact that they restructured all their media communication spending, all these were possible with access to consumer insights, analytics, and predictions. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mobile customers were encouraged to send a Unique Code printed inside the Coffee sachets to a short-code. The incentive to take action was the chance to win a free mobile Top-Up, Free branded digital content or a grand prize car!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The result of the digital reward was reaching and gaining 5 million consumers in four short months and unprecedented 100K SMS peak traffic in just one day from one country. Within the same four months, 7 million transaction records were observed, a feat that was hitherto impossible without iMakaseb&apos;s oversight of loyalty and promotion rewards, these huge recorded transactions would not have been possible with the traditional way of distributing prizes and incentives.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Traditional methods posed a lot of inefficiencies and delays in launching, iMakaseb leverage modern digital online marketing tools to deliver outstanding results.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;iMakaseb is specialized in omni-channel consumer engagement channels for physical products sold in retail and supermarkets. As industry leaders for over 6 years, this company was built to coordinate and orchestrate your marketing campaigns. The platform provides a flexible way to manage your relationships across the entire customer life-cycle. The solutions give you a 360° view of customer data, allowing you to plan and deliver personalized and real-time marketing communications resulting in greater marketing effectiveness.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;iMakaseb&apos;s platform delivers the following powerful tools: &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;360° management of customer data &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Omni-channel campaign management, like SMS, Mobile Application, QR Code, POS integration, Chatbots, Social Network Applications.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Statistical and behavioral analysis with real-time data. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more details visit iMakaseb.com&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>